Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
No living creature was hurt during
the production of this show.
Osman Bey, do you have time?
We couldn't talk.
Not now, Malhun Hatun.
Not now.
Alps!
To the potter.
Osman?
Osman Bey, spare my life!
Spare my life, Osman Bey!
If I take your life, it would be blessing.
Who are you working for? Who?
Who is holding your leashes?
Tell me! Who?
I will tell you. I will.
I will tell you everything!
The traitors are your closest ones,
Osman Bey.
Who?
-Who is that?
-The traitor is--
The arrow came this way.
Come on, alps!
Boran, go this way.
Bala...
-You stay here.
-As you order, my bey.
The arrow came from here, it seems.
-How can you be so sure?
-I saw a shadow on the window.
And the footprints prove me.
He was here.
-Who are you?
-Your death, Osman. Your death!
I'm here, Osman Bey!
-Where did you come from, nephew?
-From now, I'll always be with you!
Then, show me your valiance!
Come on, to the horses.
Give me the bow.
Come on, my lion!
My bey killed them all. Let us check
around. It's good to be cautious.
Gencebay, hold, brother.
Let us check them good.
They wore like kayı people but
there must be something else.
Come on, brother.
Come on.
We are looking but do we know what
we are looking for? No need to waste time.
We don't know, brother. We don't.
But it's good to be cautious.
Brother.
What is that?
If they are doing this in Söğüt
in the sun light...
...Osman Bey must have many enemies.
What's happening, Bala Hatun?
What's cooking here?
What is? Thank Allah, Osman Bey
can stop everyone's plans.
If Osman Bey will struggle with every
problem, why are you here, Bala Hatun?
I'm won't take lessons from you on
how to help my husband. Know your place!
I'm Umur Bey's daughter! I know my place
and what to say to anyone!
-Good.
-But it's not the time to speak.
It's time to work.
-Let's leave here.
-Let's go.
Ya Allah!
Who is this traitor, my bey?
Do you know him?
I don't know him, Bayhoca.
My nephew, I see that you leave
no burden to me.
You are fighting for the Muslim Turks,
carrying their burden, my bey.
Let us handle such small things.
My nephew, this is the path of jihad.
The one who carries the flag of Islam...
...is one with the one who cries
Allah's name in the field.
May you live long, my bey. You lead us
so we can subjugate the great mountains.
You ask for jihad, so we can destroy
the heathens.
You give the order and we will do it,
my bey.
Thank you, nephew.
Thank you. May you live long.
A Kayı warrior should speak like this.
My bey...
My bey?
The heathen is uncircumcised.
We'll find out who he is.
Who are you?
Who are you, I say!
-Where are you taking me?
-To your salvation, Dündar Bey.
-Who are you? Who are you?
-That's not the time, Dündar Bey.
Who are you serving for?
Who are you? Who are you?
Süleyman?
Bala Hatun!
-Who was the man Osman Bey caught?
-İdris.
He was a potter.
-What did he want from him?
-The price of treason.
So the traitors entered into
your tribe?
Bala.
Malhun Hatun.
What happened, my bey?
Have you caught the traitor?
We have.
We have but...
...we still have suspicions.
We followed the tracks.
It seems that the tracks won't
lead us to anywhere.
Malhun Hatun.
Tell me, is there anything we
are missing?
No, Osman Bey.
I wonder what you think.
I only think of questions.
The answers are on the corpse
of the potter.
Bala, go to the tribe with
Malhun Hatun.
As you want, my bey.
I don't know who are you or
who are you serving for...
...but don't forget that
I'm Osman Bey's uncle...
...a Kayı bey,
Dündar!
Never!
Did you forget that we saved you
from Osman Bey's wrath?
It seems that I saved you from
İdris' confession.
You are a smart man, Dündar Bey.
We both should be thankful.
We want nothing but your
good.
You helped us a lot by letting
the Cumans enter the tribe.
So, you are serving Nikola?
We serve no one but our
lord and savior Jesus Christ!
I believe that we have the same
interests...
...as much as I believe in Jesus Christ,
Dündar Bey.
What is there that I want but can't
take...
...that you will give it to me?
Just like Lord Nikola wants, we want you
to have what's your right, Dündar Bey.
The beylig.
The beylig?
You want me to betray, like Nikola.
And you say that you will make me
the bey in return.
What will happen if I refuse?
Will you kill a Kayı bey?
Of course, no.
But we can't stop your nephew
from killing you...
...after finding out that you work with
Nikola and killed İdris the Potter.
If I die, you won't get what you want.
This is the arrow of the traitor
we chased.
Whoever killed the potter...
...he isn't the man we chased.
Then, they mislead us.
It's obvious that someone is
playing with us.
My bey, we found this on one of
the traitors who stopped you.
Who are they, Osman Bey?
Whoever the snake is,
if they entered our tribe...
...there is no need to search for
it far away.
-What's your order, my bey?
-Search the potter's tent and shop.
-All right, my bey.
Send the alps to take the corpse.
Do you think he will do what
we want?
When he has Osman's bowstring
on his neck...
It's time to take care of Malhun and
her father Umur Bey.
Umur Bey accepts Osman Bey's
invitation to settle in these lands...
...this can turn into a barbarian invasion
on Bithynia.
Because Umur Bey is one of the most
renowned Turkmen beys in Anatolia.
Many other beys will follow him.
Then, Osman will leave the fur
of the bey...
...and sit on the throne of the sultan.
Nikola has no plans against
Osman's plan.
He still believes that he'll
ambush and kill Osman.
That's why we are here, brother.
These lands are sacred...
...too sacred to leave to Nikola's hands.
So, what will we do?
We'll work with the devil even
to stop Osman's invasion of Bithynia.
First, we'll take care of Umur.
His tribe has more population
than Osman's.
Osman has 500 soldiers,
Umur Bey has 1000.
You understand what does it mean,
right?
-What's on your mind?
-Geyhatu's hunting dog Toygar.
First, we'll help Toygar to
capture Umur Bey.
Then, we'll unleash Toygar upon
Osman.
This trip to Constantinople is
giving you stress, Nikola.
It must be easy for someone who
doesn't know the weight of this crown.
I don't like uninvited guests.
Especially if the uninvited guest
is good for nothing.
You won't think that way when
you hear why I came.
Let me tell you why you came, Göktuğ.
Maybe it's to tell me how you
failed in the raid?
Or maybe it's to tell me how you
still serving Osman?
If so, don't bother.
Because I have no doubts.
Maybe this will help.
-What's this?
-Osman Bey's settling plans.
Where did you find them?
While we were leaving the tribe,
I managed to hide them from Osman.
So, you have the rest, you say?
Yes. But if you want to have them...
...you should pay a price.
I'm ready to pay you the price
with gold.
But if these documents are fake,
Göktuğ...
...then you'll pay very bad.
And I will make you pay that price
when I return from Constantinople.
Flatyos, remind me that.
With great pleasure, Nikola.
Until we find out if the documents
are fake, you'll be our guest, Göktuğ.
I like caution.
Flatyos, let us host our guest in
our dungeon.
Believe me, I won't stay there for long.
You will see that the documents
are real.
Will you accompany him when
Nikola goes to Constantinople?
It's none of your business.
We searched İdris' tent, Osman Bey.
We found nothing about his treachery.
-May I enter, Osman Bey.
-Come.
Osman Bey, these are İdris' personal
belongings from his store.
Despite how much a man
wants to hide his religion...
...he will still want to carry a sign
somewhere.
To return to himself when
he is alone.
Oh, Osman Bey, oh.
Who would believe that?
He hid it from me even.
Oh, İdris, oh...
Abdurrahman Ghazi, Bamsı Bey...
...you fought with many heathens
alongside my father.
Tell me.
Who are they?
Abdurrahman Ghazi.
They are the greatest of the heathens,
Osman Bey.
The servants of the pope
carry this sign.
Then, we'll find out...
...if it was the pope's spies or someone
from the tribe who killed İdris.
May Allah forbid, do you still think that
we have traitors among us?
Inside or outside, we are running
out of time.
-May I enter, my bey?
-Come!
Where are you coming from, uncle?
I was at Söğüt, Osman Bey.
What were you doing at Söğüt?
It was about trade.
I was following your orders, my bey.
Is that so?
Were you preparing a new caravan?
Will this be like the last one?
My bey, who would've thought
of putting someone in the caravan?
Someone have.
-How did they know?
-May I enter, my bey?
Come.
News, my bey.
This is the situation...
...I witnessed a murder and found
evidence, I am convinced that...
...the blow that will defeat
Osman Bey won't come from the heathens...
...but from the Kayı Tribe.
I'll keep gathering information
until you come here.
-Take it to my bey father.
-As you order, Malhun Hatun.
What kind of trouble are you in,
Osman Bey?
How will you get out of all these
troubles?
The emperor called Nikola.
-He will move out tomorrow.
-Will we raid him, Osman Bey?
We can't stand idle, brother!
We'll strike the heathens
in everywhere we see them!
They'll be prepared.
They will hide.
They'll wait for us to set an ambush.
But we'll strike them from where
they expect the least.
-From here, it's all hills, Osman Bey.
-I know, brother.
So, I'll send the alps on foot.
Good idea.
If you allow me, I want to lead them,
Osman Bey.
You will stay here, brother.
Osman Bey, it's your order, of course.
But you choose me as the First Alp.
Do you regret that?
When I'm on a campaign,
I'm the First Alp, brother.
You'll stay in the tribe.
Here is also in danger.
-Last time my nephew--
-Uncle!
You'll stay here with my brother.
And you won't leave here
no matter what.
No one will enter our tribe without
my knowledge.
As you order, Osman Bey.
Uncle, you will obey whatever
my brother says.
Bamsı Bey, what do you say?
How should we attack?
If they know that we'll ambush,
they'll come crowded.
There will be many martyrs.
There will be many martyrs, Osman Bey.
This will be as dangerous as it
taker longer.
It will be a great jihad.
Everyone should get ready.
So, tell me now.
Should we take Göktuğ's head
for deceiving us...
...or should we give him what he wants?
-The documents are real.
-Does he have the rest of them?
-He says that he has it all.
Do you think that we can trust
Göktuğ, Flatyos?
I don't trust anyone for saving
my life once.
But Göktuğ has no other choice.
I'm sure he'll take us to the documents.
I will bring the gold.
Osman will ambush Nikola.
I will inform Süleyman about that.
Osman will be ambushed
on his way to an ambush.
Dündar Bey...
If Osman dies among all the alps...
...no one will return.
-So?
-So...
...you want to be the bey but
tell me...
If everyone dies, whose bey will you be?
Do you think I'm a boy, woman?
After I sit on the fur of the bey,
I'll think of that as well.
Why are you stressed?
My thumb ring is missing, woman.
I'm thinking about it.
Maybe you dropped it while shooting?
No, it was on my thumb then.
It must've fallen when I was
going to Süleyman's shop.
So, why don't you search for it
before anyone else finds it?
I'll look when I'm going to Süleyman.
Just another trouble. Who knows
how we'll save ourselves.
Traders want markets.
Ghazis want jihad.
A great conquest will have us
heard from everywhere.
Then, the ghazis will join us.
The path for new markets will
be opened.
Traders will come.
Osman is right, daughter.
If his heir will be a bey...
...then, the mother should be
a bey's daughter.
You are right, mother.
You are right.
But a bey's daughter,
especially the one who'll give a heir...
Will enter the tent and kick you...
...out of the tent and Osman's
heart, you think.
Don't worry. No one can replace you.
Neither from this tent
nor from Osman's heart.
A great conquest.
We need a great victory.
May I enter, Osman Bey?
Come.
What's wrong, Malhun Hatun?
Where will we settle in, Osman Bey?
Tell me.
So, you want to hear it as soon
as possible.
Is there a need to wait?
The home I want to give you is
around Bolu.
-Why there?
-Big lands, big grasslands.
Counsel with Umur Bey. If he thinks
it's appropriate, settle there.
That can't be.
I learned about these lands before
I came. We can't trade there.
We don't only want to be shepherds
but traders too.
Show us such a place that we'll be close
to trade centers.
So, you learned about our lands?
-So, you want to trade?
-The hand that gives is superior.
Give, so that you'll be superior.
Give, so that we'll stand with you.
And crush your enemies.
Be your shield against the traitors.
Think about that, Osman Bey.
Malhun Hatun!
Wait.
Umur Bey raised you well.
If you had accepted that land,
you would lose my favor.
These lands are your new home.
May it be good.
Dündar Bey will help you.
Tell me if you need anything.
You won't regret it, Osman Bey.
A bey's daughter.
May I enter, Osman Bey.
Come, aunt.
You wanted to see me.
You have things to say.
Aunt...
My dear aunt...
-I wish one thing from you.
-Not wish, your words are my orders.
Not at all, aunt.
Not at all.
Tell me, Osman Bey.
Your tribe is also invited, aunt.
I want you to leave us with your
longing.
Go, go and bring your tribe here.
-You mean my siblings, huh?
-Yes.
It's been so long.
I miss them.
Convince them to come to
these lands, aunt.
Send them my regards.
And tell them that Osman Bey
is inviting them.
Of course, I will, son.
But tell me.
How will I bear this longing?
Make way!
With the name of Allah.
-Salam Alaikum.
-Alaikum Salam.
Dündar Bey is here too.
I wanted to be blessed with
your words, my sheikh.
Not at all.
With the name of Allah.
Longing is better than a reunion,
my friends.
But it's still good to
reunite.
We reunited with our loved one
and returned, thank Allah.
We missed him again already.
Tell me, my friends.
How are you?
Thank Allah.
Türker Hasan how is your business
in Söğüt?
-Thank Allah, my sheikh
-Thank Allah, of course.
We should be thankful for what
we have and what we don't have.
For the good and the bad.
It will increase with thankfulness
and decrease with complaints.
Don't say it's little, it will be little.
Say it's a lot, it will be a lot.
If people stop being grateful
in a country...
...they won't have prosperity.
We saw that Söğüt market
is in prospertiy. Mashallah.
Tell me now, how are your
relations with non-muslim neighbors?
We are good.
Mercy is worse than treason.
How can a cruel man show mercy?
Of course, there can be, my sheikh.
Mercy can take a man's faith.
We missed this foresight, Kumral.
We heard and learned from
Sage Tapduk.
Let me tell you.
Who said that?
Priest Odon.
Where did he say that?
Sultan Gıyaseddin's city, Antalya's
Elmalı.
Do you know Elmalı? Had anyone been
there?
We know, my bey.
We know.
It's not our place to talk about battles
when Dündar Bey is here.
Not at all, my sheikh.
Not at all.
When İmameddin Zengi of Mosul...
...took Urfo from heathen Joselin...
...European heathens came together
and started a campaign.
Glorious Sultan Mesut wasn't going to
let the heathens succeed...
...so he took all the way through
Anatolia.
He broke one arm of the crusader
army in Eskişehir...
...and the other part wanted to
pass the Toros mountains.
They came...
...they set camp at Toros
mountains.
Crusaders had hundreds of thousands
of soldiers.
So, what do that many
soldiers need?
Heathens get hungry too. They need
food, water...
True. In time...
...the crusaders were left without
any food.
They will seize the food of
the people.
And 3 out of 4 houses...
...are made of Rum families.
So, the Rum people that they
embraced...
...ran to the Turks of Elmalı
to save their food.
They even fought with the heathens
in the ranks of the Turks.
Crusaders finally surendered.
The legends say that 3000 of them
asked for mercy.
A Muslim can't hit the one
who ask for mercy.
So, 3000 crusaders...
...converts to Islam and settles
in Elmalı.
That's why the priest said that.
Mercy is worse than treason.
Mercy to humans, mercy to animals...
From an ant to an elephant; mercy!
The flag of the Kayı
is the flag of Islam.
You came here with nothing but
swords and you conquered here.
Swords take lands but...
...to settle in that lands...
...you should mercy to...
...everything on these lands.
Those who don't have mercy,
can't have faith.
That's it, my friends.
That's enough for now.
-I shouldn't take your time.
-Not at all.
Mother!
Bayhoca? I'm here, son.
-Mother? Did I call you?
-You wandered about me.
I had a dream, mother.
I'm fine.
-Was it a nightmare?
-No, mother. I'm fine.
You are sweating.
Tell me what did you see.
-It's not bad, mother. Don't worry.
-Good then...
...tell me if it's good.
It was a pure white place.
-Like a house?
-I don't know. It was white.
A bird got out of my mouth.
It flew away.
It became invisible.
It was like it was flying
away from a cage.
-What kind of a bird was it?
-What kind, mother?
A dream bird of course.
Mother, you look sleepless.
I will sleep if you allow me.
Sleep, son.
It seems that you have news for me,
Dündar 'Bey'.
I can't wait to hear it.
What's that good news?
You are lucky.
The documents are real.
Did you doubt it.
I owe you my life. But as
you can understand, Nikola had doubts.
He freed him of his doubts?
You'll find out when you meet him
for the gold. You are free now.
Flatyos.
There are no more doubts,
no more treason.
There will be gold for my service.
Göktuğ, Nikola's friendship is
much more valuable than gold.
You will see that.
I don't doubt that.
-My bey, if Nikola gets these...
-He will, Göktuğ. He will.
You will give them to Nikola.
-I will?
-You will.
You will give these unimportant
documents to Nikola.
So that we can find out who he
is allied to.
All right, my bey.
All right.
Aunt.
Bey of the Kayı, may Allah
give you health.
Aunt, you are the post of this
tribe.
Kayı women learned how to be
woman from you.
It's time. Remind Kayı beys how to
be a bey.
I'm grateful.
I'm thankful, aunt.
Osman, you deserved the fur,
I defended that right.
I saw you as the bey,
inshallah I'll see your state as well.
Inshallah, aunt.
Inshallah.
Women want to say farewell too.
Mashallah to my girls.
You are like angels.
May Allah destine you everything you want.
May you never have grief.
You are leaving us motherless,
Mother Selcan. No grief, huh?
-What other grief do we need?
-Daughter...
My pretty daughter...
Bala...
You are leaving me both motherless
and fatherless.
-You were both my mother and my father.
-Daughter...
...why are you talking like
I will not return?
Promise me, mother.
Promise me that you'll return.
Destiny. If it's in our destiny,
inshallah I will return.
Aygül... Aygül...
Aygül...
Mother, which words can describe
your efforts on me?
-What gratefulness can answer you?
-What are you saying, daughter?
I had darkness in my heart,
you were my light.
I forgot what it meant to be a woman.
You taught me.
You taught me to fight
and stand.
You will burn my heart, my daughter.
Aygül, you will take good
care of your son, will you?
You will teach what I taught you.
From now, you have my place.
Thank Allah,
Bala has Osman...
...Gonca has Boran.
You will marry again,
build a home.
-Come on.
-Selcan Hatun.
Forgive me.
Forgiveness is for Allah, daughter.
I understand you and know your heart.
-Give me your blessing.
-It's yours.
Now is the time to leave.
Take care of each other.
Son, it's time to leave.
Godspeed.
Alps! Here...
...is where the war begins.
Now...
...you all will be alone with
your weapons.
May Allah give you strength
and courage!
Allahu Akbar!
Now, when we leave the battlefield
victorious...
...your shouts will tremble the sky!
-Amin!
Now, we'll continue on foot
from here.
We'll set our traps on the road
and set ambushes.
-May Allah bless our efforts!
-Allahu Akbar! Allahu Akbar!
What a good day, isn't it?
Helen?
It's good to see you happy, Nikola.
I thought you would be stressed on
your way to Constantinople.
If I wasn't taking a good present to
the emperor, I would be.
-What's that good present?
-That secret is for me, Helen.
Nikola, I'm grateful that you took
me with you.
Holy Lord, this is very exciting.
How could I keep you out
of this joy?
I feel like this will be a lot
more fun I think.
I will tell you on the way.
I'm very excited, Helen.
Bring it, daughter.
Bring it. May Allah bless your hands.
With the name of Allah.
What's up, Hazal? You are so happy.
Is it because Selcan Hatun left?
Lena. Lena!
Stop it now. Aren't you happy
because Selcan Hatun left?
-Didn't she bother you a lot?
-Right.
She didn't bother me enough.
May I enter?
Come.
Come, daughter.
Come, come.
-Drink our sherbet. Come.
-I have no time. I'm looking for Dündar Bey.
What will you do with Dündar Bey?
We want to accept Osman Bey's invite
and settle on the borders.
He wanted Dündar Bey to take care
of our settling.
Don't worry, daughter.
My husband won't leave you alone.
I know, Hazal Hatun.
I know.
But what I didn't know is...
...that Osman Bey was that much
in trouble.
There is nothing Osman Bey can't
get over, don't worry.
True. But even a mountain can't
stand against treachery.
A traitor was killed in front of
his eyes.
If it wasn't for Allah, it could be him.
Who knows, daughter. Maybe it was
Nikola, maybe it was the Mongols.
Maybe it was someone from the tribe.
I heard that both Savcı Bey and
Dündar Bey was in quarrel with him.
What do you mean, Malhun Hatun?
But thank Allah that it didn't
go any further.
Ertuğrul Bey's blood knew how
to be together.
You are right. Despite all that,
Osman Bey saved our son.
He took him out of the
castle of the heathens.
That's where the Kayı
get their strength.
In difficult times, they know how
to stand together.
Thank Allah.
May Allah give Osman Bey
a long life.
May Allah protect him.
Amin.
Whatever the truth is, it will be
revealed. Sooner or later.
It will. Of course.
Dündar Bey is at Söğüt, my pretty girl.
I should leave, then. We'll have plenty
of time to drink sherbet.
Of course, we will have.
-If you allow me.
-Of course.
That girl. What is she going after?
What is she trying to do?
The truth.
My bey, our alps are positioned
on that hill.
-Have the archers positioned?
-They have, my bey.
-We positioned the rocks as you ordered.
-No one will move without an order.
-Brother.
You were like him when you were young.
Always competing with the older ones.
We learned courage from our older
brothers.
Be careful, my son.
Don't put yourself or your father
in danger.
Don't worry, mother. We'll strike
the heathens and return safe and sound.
Don't worry, my wife.
He is a Kayı bey. He goes to
live his destiny.
We are destined with jihad.
You know it.
And our son prefers to fight with a sword
and not be a shepherd.
You should get used to it.
Come on, son.
Bayhoca is a worthy Kayı bey.
I missed my son's childhood, Osman Bey.
He was in madrasahs,
he was getting education.
Now, he has a sword in one hand
and a pencil on the other.
We had enough of longing.
Now I won't keep him away from me.
Osman Bey, I'm grateful that you
took me to this jihad.
Thank you.
We had to take you.
If we hadn't, you would follow us.
Come on. Don't bow your head.
A Kayı bey stands straight.
You are our future, Bayhoca.
It's not about joining the jihad but
not listening to your bey.
It won't happen again, my bey.
I'll fight alongside my brave father,
and my bey uncle. I can die now.
Return to the alps now.
We'll swing swords in many more
battles, inshallah.
Inshallah, brother.
Inshallah.
I'm hungry again.
- You're hungry? Again?
- Huh.
Eat it.
You'll fight.
You have to be strong.
What about you?
I won't let people be hungry.
- Even...
- Even?
You.
Take it, mad girl.
You should eat.
I'm not hungry.
It's a sign.
Nikola is coming.
- Let's tell them
- Come on.
- May it be easy.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
My Gonca.
What you're thinking
makes you happy, I guess.
What is going on with you?
What am I thinking?
Boran Alp.
Don't you think about marrying him...
when he comes back?
Bala.
May it be easy, Hatuns.
Thank you.
If you're here to help...
take it.
Hatun of Bey saturates people.
We hold swords.
I wonder who is the killer of the potter.
Did your Alps find any trace?
They will, Hatun.
Sooner or later.
Are you waiting for another death?
Why are you so concerned?
Don't you have work
with Dündar Bey anyway?
Mashallah, you hear everything.
Hatun of Bey...
stands with her Bey, not his behind.
If he stands with him, she'll know what
happens in her tent.
So that you're a Hatun of Bey...
then listen to me well.
My tent is ready for Osman Bey.
Osman Bey's enemies may
become our enemies one day.
I'm the daughter of a Bey, Bala Hatun.
My tent's safety comes first.
Then go to your tent.
Don't make Dündar Bey wait.
May it be easy.
If you excuse me.
Bala.
Something's wrong with her.
She is always in troubling situations.
She'll go anyway.
Until then, we'll keep an eye on her.
My Bey.
Tell me.
We have a sign from the watchmen.
Nikola and his soldiers are close.
Do we have...
equal soldiers?
Yes.
My Alps.
My valiants.
As Bamsı Bey said...
if this keeps any longer...
this will be more dangerous.
So, we should kill Nikola...
and leave here immediately.
I know...
we'll have martyrs.
we'll die.
However...
we won't let our sanjak down.
Yes, my Bey!
Come on.
It's like I have seen Osman Bey's
condition.
My brave daughter.
My light.
My special child...
who doesn't let me feel the absence
of my martyr children.
My Malhun.
What are you thinking...
about what she wrote?
She says he has many enemies.
He has few friends.
Osman Bey has so many unbelievers around.
All around him is Byzantine.
He can't go any land.
He won't take lands from Germiyanids.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim. (in the name of Allah, the merciful and compassionate.)
A Beylic is ancestral.
It's not eternal.
His grandfather Suleyman Shah...
came from Aleppo yesterday.
We've fought for Seljuqs for many years.
What we have is that
everyone has a part of it!
Did Mongols come to share out Seljuqs'
property to those Beys, Bahadır Bey?
Chobanids, Germiyanids and the others...
all of them have their thrones.
Some of them still...
run away from Mongols.
We can't count how many of his
soldiers that Geyhatu has killed.
However, thank Allah that you're alive.
My Bey. Sarıcahan is ready for
tomorrow's accommodation.
Send two more men.
They should go in disguised.
- They don't know others.
- Your command.
My Bey.
Is it even possible for Seljuqs' heritage that
even Kızılbeyoğulları hasn't received...
to be received by Osman
Bey, son of Ertuğrul Ghazi?
Either he will conquer Tekfur Castle and
he will found his state in Bitinya...
or he'll give up on his Beyhood.
Let's say we're in the lands
that Osman has shown us...
what if Osman attacks?
What if what you've said happens?
What happens to Bayandur Tribe then?
Kızılbeyoğlu will be Umur Bey's.
Aren't Kayı Tribe and...
Bayandur Tribe together anyway?
Isn't our sanjak is Turk, Bahadır Bey?
- Yes.
- So...
Let's say Osman got weak...
and his sanjak is down...
will we let Byzantine take what we have?
However...
we have seen.
We know tradition.
We care about Bayandur's peace.
Who gives happiness is my Allah.
Nikola.
Wait for my sign.
Come on.
Attack!
Get ready for the battle order!
Protect Nikola!
Allah is eternal!
Attack!
Come on, valiants.
Bayhoca!
Bayhoca! Alps!
Son!
- Son!
- Bayhoca!
Son!
You'll be okay, son.
Brother!
My son!
You'll be fine. You'll be
fine, my valiant.
Hold on, my son.
My son.
Dündar Bey, Aygül Hatun
left with Osman Bey.
Yes. She is the leader of Bacıs.
What, daughter?
Are you here to eat?
I ate, Dündar Bey.
Thank you.
I wanted to see Söğüt.
- I have some questions.
- Tell me.
What are they?
Osman Bey said that you'll be
dealing with settlement. (lodging)
We'll talk about it when
your father comes.
Now, I have some work to do.
Sit.
There are some things to be done before
my father comes.
My father trusts me.
However...
does Osman Bey trust his uncle?
What...
What are you saying?
He doesn't go to war with you anymore.
But you're powerful in wars.
Yes, I am and...
when Osman Bey wants me, I'll go to war.
However...
he has something else to do now.
Osman Bey doesn't
need his old uncle anyway.
May Allah make your respect
and loyalty for Osman Bey everlasting.
Yes.
Let's start with water wells that are
placed on where the tent will be.
I'm listening.
Tell me.
Son!
Son...
Osman knows you're going to Byzantine.
How can he know?
What matters is that he knows.
He'll set a trap for you.
It's not about it!
- How can he know!
- Don't dare to attack me again.
Petrus.
You're in my castle.
We're friends, Nikola.
Friends don't attack each other.
Instead of being angry...
think of how you'll capture Osman.
How do...
how do you know about...
Osman's trap?
Dündar Bey.
He is in our pocket.
- Dündar?
- Yes.
He is in our pocket now.
Hold on, son.
Hold on, my valiant. Hold on!
Hold on!
My brother!
A real commander...
sacrifices his name for many people!
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com